<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Sebastián Aranda Page on Sebastián Aranda Sánchez website</title>
    <link>http://www.sebastianaranda.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Sebastián Aranda Page on Sebastián Aranda Sánchez website</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Nov 2020 16:22:37 -0300</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://www.sebastianaranda.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Spectral Line Classification</title>
      <link>http://www.sebastianaranda.com/projects/spectral-line-classification-llda/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Nov 2020 16:22:37 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.sebastianaranda.com/projects/spectral-line-classification-llda/</guid>
      <description>Labeled Latent Dirichlet Allocation model implementation for spectral line classification on ALMA Astronomy Datacubes
The discipline of astroinformatics has grown a lot over the past few years thanks to the creation of bigger and more sophisticated telescopes, such as the Atacama Large Millimeter/submillimeter Array. With better spectral resolution in data, a new challenge is set in the way astronomical data is analyzed. In particular, data cubes produced by radioastronomy projects have generated an explosion in the volume of data retrieved.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About me</title>
      <link>http://www.sebastianaranda.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Nov 2020 16:05:25 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.sebastianaranda.com/about/</guid>
      <description>My dream To work in astronomy and computing: I consider myself a great programmer, but I would love to put my skills at the service of astronomy.
Who am I Hello, I am a computer engineer who loves science and astronomy. I&amp;rsquo;ve studied at Federico Santa María Technical University, where I&amp;rsquo;ve learned most of my academic knowledge. I like multidisciplinary work spaces, learn from others and generate solutions together is my motivation.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
