<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Sebastian Aranda Sanchez website on Sebastian Aranda Sánchez website</title>
    <link>https://www.sebastianaranda.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Sebastian Aranda Sanchez website on Sebastian Aranda Sánchez website</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Sebastian Aranda Sanchez</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.sebastianaranda.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>LOVE</title>
      <link>https://www.sebastianaranda.com/projects/inria/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 16:11:37 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.sebastianaranda.com/projects/inria/</guid>
      <description>When From Oct 2020 to Today
Where At INRIA for collaboration with the Vera C. Rubin Observatory.
What I&amp;rsquo;ve worked as programmer and currently project leader of LOVE, the LSST Operators Visualization Environment, a system to monitor several components of the Vera C. Rubin Observatory. This Observatory has over 65 subsystems that monitors different aspects of the telescope and its environment. LOVE is connected to the mayority of these systems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Services</title>
      <link>https://www.sebastianaranda.com/services/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.sebastianaranda.com/services/</guid>
      <description>Software Development I&amp;rsquo;ve developed several web applications for small and big companies. If you need to build a website or application, from a simple landing page to a more complex system such as an ERP, I can give you a hand: designing, developing, deploying, hosting and mantining the sofware you need.
 IT Support I really like to solve problems. I can provide support with different kind of computer problems: hardware diagnostics, software reparation, troubleshooting and customer support.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learning Management Systems</title>
      <link>https://www.sebastianaranda.com/projects/enovus/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Nov 2020 16:22:37 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.sebastianaranda.com/projects/enovus/</guid>
      <description>When From Aug 2014 to Feb 2020
Where At ENOVUS
What I&amp;rsquo;ve worked implementing a lot of LMS systems (Learning Management Systems) used for e-learning education. I&amp;rsquo;ve developed several components of different kind, in Frontend and Backend. Also worked with a lot of clients, using and agile approach with regular meetings to indentify, discuss and validate requirements.
How Frontend: HMTL, CSS, CSS3, SASS, Javascript
Backend: AMP stack (Apache, Mysql -Maria DB- and PHP)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Native Applications</title>
      <link>https://www.sebastianaranda.com/projects/osare/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Nov 2020 16:22:37 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.sebastianaranda.com/projects/osare/</guid>
      <description>When From 2014 to Feb 2017
Where At OSARE
What I&amp;rsquo;ve participated on the creation an entrepreneurship company called OSARE, we focused on developing innovative apps. This was one of my first job approachs, so it was the beginning of my development carrer. We were able to develop two applicaitons:
 HelpyCar: an application used to geolocate car workshops in case you required any urgent service. This was developed in native Android and we never did a release, but it served as a first approach to the software development.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spectral Line Classification</title>
      <link>https://www.sebastianaranda.com/projects/spectral-line-classification-llda/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Nov 2020 16:22:37 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.sebastianaranda.com/projects/spectral-line-classification-llda/</guid>
      <description>Labeled Latent Dirichlet Allocation model implementation for spectral line classification on ALMA Astronomy Datacubes
The discipline of astroinformatics has grown a lot over the past few years thanks to the creation of bigger and more sophisticated telescopes, such as the Atacama Large Millimeter/submillimeter Array. With better spectral resolution in data, a new challenge is set in the way astronomical data is analyzed. In particular, data cubes produced by radioastronomy projects have generated an explosion in the volume of data retrieved.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About me</title>
      <link>https://www.sebastianaranda.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Nov 2020 16:05:25 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.sebastianaranda.com/about/</guid>
      <description>Who I am Hello, my name is Sebastian Aranda Sanchez, mainly known as Seba and I&amp;rsquo;m a Chilean Computer Engineer who loves Science and Astronomy. My interests in technology comes since I&amp;rsquo;m a child as I love video games, hence my cercany to the field. I&amp;rsquo;ve studied at Federico Santa María Technical University, where I&amp;rsquo;ve learned most of my academic knowledge. I&amp;rsquo;ve benn working in Informatic from at least 6 years (in stable jobs and also some failed ventures), mainly focused on Web Development.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>