<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Sebastian Aranda Sanchez website on Sebastián Aranda Sánchez website</title>
    <link>https://www.sebastianaranda.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Sebastian Aranda Sanchez website on Sebastián Aranda Sánchez website</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Nov 2020 16:22:37 -0300</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.sebastianaranda.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Learning Management Systems</title>
      <link>https://www.sebastianaranda.com/projects/jobs/enovus/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Nov 2020 16:22:37 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.sebastianaranda.com/projects/jobs/enovus/</guid>
      <description>Where At ENOVUS
What I&amp;rsquo;ve worked implementing a lot of LMS systems (Learning Management Systems) used for e-learning education. I&amp;rsquo;ve developed several components of different kind, in Frontend and Backend. Also worked with a lot of clients, using and agile approach with regular meetings to indentify, discuss and validate requirements.
How Frontend: HMTL, CSS, CSS3, SASS, Javascript
Backend: AMP stack (Apache, Mysql -Maria DB- and PHP)
Tools: Navicat, Trello, Mailgun, SENCE integration</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spectral Line Classification</title>
      <link>https://www.sebastianaranda.com/projects/personal/spectral-line-classification-llda/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Nov 2020 16:22:37 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.sebastianaranda.com/projects/personal/spectral-line-classification-llda/</guid>
      <description>Labeled Latent Dirichlet Allocation model implementation for spectral line classification on ALMA Astronomy Datacubes
The discipline of astroinformatics has grown a lot over the past few years thanks to the creation of bigger and more sophisticated telescopes, such as the Atacama Large Millimeter/submillimeter Array. With better spectral resolution in data, a new challenge is set in the way astronomical data is analyzed. In particular, data cubes produced by radioastronomy projects have generated an explosion in the volume of data retrieved.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About me</title>
      <link>https://www.sebastianaranda.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Nov 2020 16:05:25 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.sebastianaranda.com/about/</guid>
      <description>Who I am Hello, my name is Sebastian Aranda Sanchez, mainly known as Seba and I&amp;rsquo;m a computer engineer who loves science and astronomy. I&amp;rsquo;ve studied at Federico Santa María Technical University, where I&amp;rsquo;ve learned most of my academic knowledge. I like multidisciplinary work spaces, learn from others and generate solutions together, that is my motivation. I am very structured, commited and disciplined with my work, give me any problem and I&amp;rsquo;ll find the way to solve it.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
